Guide to the Betty C. Jukes Papers
University of Houston Libraries
- Arts Philanthropy, id163710
  - West Point Cadets' Glee Club Concerts, id163879
    - Invitations, Response Cards, and Tickets, 1979-1981; id164098 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, 1981-1988; id164099 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, 1978-1979; id164100 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1980-1981; id164101 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Member and Cadet Lists, 1978-1981; id164102 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Ads and Appearances, and Blank Forms, 1978-1981; id164103 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Financials, 1979-1981; id164104 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Notes, 1979-1981; id164105 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Charts and Floor Plans, 1978-1981; id164106 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Photos, 1978-1982; id164107 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Audio Reel, undated; id164108 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Houston Grand Opera and TUTS, id163880
    - Houston Grand Opera Programs and Correspondence, id164110 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Houston Symphony Society - Women's Committee, id163881
    - Member and Officer Lists, 1974-1976; id164112 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Concert Programs, 1973-1976; id164113 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1975-2001; id164114 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Yearbooks, 1971-1975; id164115 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Yearbooks, 1976-1991; id164116 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Press, Publicity, and Bios, id164117 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Organizational Materials and Notes, 1975; id164118 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Houston Museums, id163882
    - Museum of Fine Arts and Houston Museum of Natural Science, 1975-1986; id164120 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Health Advocacy and Volunteer Work, id163711
  This series contains materials from Betty Jukes’ work related to St. Joseph’s Hospital, St. Luke’s Hospital, the Huffington Center on Aging, the Mental Health Association of Texas, the American Cancer Society, and the Houston March of Dimes.
  - St. Joseph's Hospital, id163883
    - Informational Sheets and Newsletters, 1970-1981; id164122 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Notes, Minutes, and Financials, 1972-1991; id164123 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Miscellanea, id164124 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1991; id164125 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Other Houston Hospitals, id163884
    - Newsletters, 1974-1978; id164127 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Newsletters, 1979-1983; id164128 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Huffington Center on Aging, id163885
    - Event Programs, 1997-1999; id164130 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Notes, 1997-1999; id164131 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1997; id164132 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1998; id164133 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1999-2012; id164134 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, undated; id164135 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Miscellanea, 1997; id164136 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Women's Health Summit Manual, 1998; id164137 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Guest Lists, Scenarios, and Seating Charts, 1998; id164138 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Biographies and Fact Sheets, 1998-1999; id164139 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Women's Health Summit Invitations, 1997-1998; id164140 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Newsletters, 1997-2000; id164141 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Photos, 1998; id164142 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Publicity, 1998-1999; id164143 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Mental Health Association of Houston, id163886
    - Miscellaneous Memorabilia and Notes, 1980; id164145 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Photos, 1979-1981; id164146 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence and Invitations, 1980; id164147 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Financials, Schedules, and Guest Lists, 1980; id164148 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Biographical Sketches and Press Releases, 1980; id164149 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - American Cancer Society, id163887
    - American Cancer Society, 1983; id164151 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - March of Dimes, id163888
    - Press, 1971-1975; id164153 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Photos, 1971-1975; id164154 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Biographies and Fact Sheets, 1981; id164155 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Programs, 1972-1976; id164156 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Programs, 1977-1983; id164157 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Guest Lists and Nominee Lists, 1972-1973; id164158 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Invitations, 1971-1983; id164159 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence, 1971-1979; id164160 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Financials, 1972-1973; id164161 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Event Planning Miscellanea, 1972-1975; id164162 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Silver Screen Gourmet Gala Invitation, 1982; id164163 (Box 18, Folder 31)
- Miscellaneous Philanthropic and Volunteer Work, id163712
  This series contains miscellaneous photos related to Houston public works and parks. Additionally, materials from the short-lived Aquarium Society of Houston and other miscellaneous philanthropic projects of Betty Jukes’ reside here.
  - Photos, id163889
    - Miscellaneous Photos, undated; id164165 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Buffalo Bayou Photos, 1998; id164166 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - City of Houston Photos, undated; id164167 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Aquarium Society of Houston, id163890
    - By-Laws, 2000; id164169 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Meeting Minutes, Notes, and Financials, 2000; id164170 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 2000; id164171 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Philanthropy, id163891
    - Northwood University Board, 1980-1996; id164173 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Houston Baptist University, 1968; id164174 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Nonprofit Marketing Strategies, General, 1988-1999; id164175 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Houston Public Library, 1983; id164176 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous Press, Articles by Betty Jukes, 1999-2008; id164177 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - 50th Annual Congress of Cities, 1974-1975; id164178 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Newcomer's Club of Greater Houston, 1992-1994; id164179 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Kincaid School, 1974-1982; id164180 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous Newsletters and Correspondence, 1974-1984; id164181 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous Event Programs, 1980-1983; id164182 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous Invitations, 1982-1983; id164183 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous Détente Ball, 1975-1983; id164184 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous Delicate Papers, 1918-1966; id164185 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Pearls of Pakistan, 1978; id164186 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Scrapbooks, Ephemera, and News Clippings, id163713
  - Scrapbooks, id163892
    - The Woman's Club of Houston Scrapbook, 1973-1975; id164191 (Box 20, Item 1)
    - Woman's Club Scrapbook, 1974-1975; id164192 (Box 20, Item 2)
    - Woman's Club Scrapbook (purple), 1975; id164193 (Box 20, Item 3)
    - March of Dimes National Register (black binder), undated; id164194 (Box 20, Item 4)
    - University of Houston "Grand Ladies" Scrapbook, undated; id164195 (Box 20, Item 5)
    - Moores School of Music Annual Luncheon Scrapbook, 1997; id164196 (Box 20, Item 6)
    - Clean Houston Synopsis Scrapbook, 1984; id164197 (Box 20, Item 7)
    - Committed: The 100-Year History of The Woman's Club of Houston, 1893-1993; id164198 (Box 20, Item 8)
    - Moores School of Music Grand Opening "Misc. Photos", 1996; id164199 (Box 21, Item 1)
    - March of Dimes Scrapbook (green binder), 1973-1976; id164200 (Box 21, Item 2)
    - Moores Opera House Grand Opening Scrapbook, 1997; id164201 (Box 21, Item 3)
    - The Woman's Club Making Bev Sills and Honorary Member, 1973-1974; id164202 (Box 21, Item 4)
    - "U.H. MOORES SCHOOL OF MUSIC" Scrapbook, 1997; id164203 (Box 22, Item 1)
    - "THE WOMAN'S CLUB OF HOUSTON" Scrapbook, 1974-1976; id164204 (Box 22, Item 2)
    - Moores School of Music "Six Evenings of Note" Scrapbook, 1997; id164205 (Box 22, Item 3)
    - "THE WOMAN'S CLUB OF HOUSTON" Yearbook Binder, 1990; id164206 (Box 22, Item 4)
    - "THE WOMAN'S CLUB OF HOUSTON" Yearbook Binder, 1991; id164207 (Box 22, Item 5)
    - "FIRST JUNIOR WOMAN'S CLUB" Yearbook Binder, 1966; id164208 (Box 22, Item 6)
    - "THE WOMAN'S CLUB OF HOUSTON" Yearbook Binder, 1990; id164209 (Box 22, Item 7)
    - "The Woman's Club of Houston" Yearbook Binder, 1992; id164210 (Box 22, Item 8)
    - "The Woman's Club of Houston" Yearbook Binder, undated; id164211 (Box 22, Item 9)
    - "THE WOMAN'S CLUB OF HOUSTON" Yearbook Binder (blue), undated; id164212 (Box 22, Item 10)
    - Houston Youth Symphony Cultural Leader of the Year Scrapbook, 1988-1991; id164213 (Box 23, Item 1)
    - Houston Youth Symphony and Ballet Scrapbook, 1989-1991; id164214 (Box 23, Item 2)
    - The Woman's Club 82nd Anniversary Scrapbook, 1974; id164215 (Box 23, Item 3)
    - "UH PARTIES" Scrapbook, undated; id164216 (Box 23, Item 4)
    - Houston Youth Symphony and Ballet Scrapbook, 1988-1989; id164217 (Box 23, Item 5)
    - HJWC Scrapbook, 1968; id164243 (Ovsbox 27, Item 1)
  - Ephemera, id163893
    - 50th Annual Congress of Cities Nametag - Betty Jukes, December 1974; id164219 (Box 24, Item 1)
    - Texas Municipal Leagues Annual Conference Nametag - Lillain Heath, October 1975; id164220 (Box 24, Item 2)
    - "DON'T SPOIL THE SOIL, RECYCLE USED OIL: Muscular Dystrophy Association" Button, undated; id164221 (Box 24, Item 3)
    - "Captain Clean: Honorary Chairman of Litter League Clean Houston" Button, undated; id164222 (Box 24, Item 4)
    - Clean Houston "OP': 1985" Button, id164223 (Box 24, Item 5)
    - "Celan Houston: Just a Pick-Up Away!" Button (4 copies), undated; id164224 (Box 24, Item 6)
    - "Warner (heart)'s The National Fitness Classic at the Houstonian, May 13-15, 1983", May 1983; id164225 (Box 24, Item 7)
    - Armstrong Ranch Matchbook, 1982; id164226 (Box 24, Item 8)
    - World Wildlife Fund - U.S. Matchbook, November 1982; id164227 (Box 24, Item 9)
    - Charles A. Lindbergh 50th Anniversary Commemorative Medallion, 1977; id164228 (Box 24, Item 10)
    - Houston Hunter and Jumper Charity Show "Sponsor" Button (2 copies), undated; id164229 (Box 24, Item 11)
    - "Keep Texas Beautiful" Button (2 copies), undated; id164230 (Box 24, Item 12)
    - "Season's Greetings from UH D" Golden Snowflake, undated; id164231 (Box 24, Item 13)
    - "Beautify Texas Council: K.T.B.C.T." Embroidered Fabric Patch, undated; id164232 (Box 24, Item 14)
    - Houston Youth Symphony Embroidered Fabric Patch (2 copies), undated; id164233 (Box 24, Item 15)
    - "Enjoy Coca-Cola" Commemorative Pen, undated; id164234 (Box 24, Item 16)
    - "Houston's Pioneer Women & Today's Leaders: 100 Years" Glass Coaster (2 copies), 2000; id164235 (Box 24, Item 17)
    - "Armstrong Ranch: Half Moon Brand" Branded Leather Medallion, 1982; id164236 (Box 24, Item 18)
    - Florist's Card addressed to Betty Jukes, undated; id164237 (Box 24, Item 19)
    - UH MSM "Six Evenings of Note" CD (3 copies), 1997; id164238 (Box 24, Item 20)
    - "40 Years of HJWC" DVD, 2008; id164239 (Box 24, Item 21)
  - News Clippings, id163894
    - "Clean Houston selling trash bags to help fund beautification program", Houston Chronicle, April 1987; id164244 (Ovsbox 25, Item 1)
    - "Clean Houston peddling trash bags to help fund beautification program", Houston Chronicle, April 1987; id164245 (Ovsbox 25, Item 2)
    - "Clean up Houston with donation", Houston Chronicle, 1987; id164246 (Ovsbox 25, Item 3)
    - "Mayor to Throw the Switch on First Annual Courtlandt Place Outdoor Christmas Tree", TOWN, December 1985; id164247 (Ovsbox 25, Item 4)
    - "Chamber Dateline: Clean Houston Honors Chamber Volunteers, Staff", Houston Magazine, January 1986; id164248 (Ovsbox 25, Item 5)
    - "Holford puts in a long night; gunman a hit" (Houston School for the Deaf), Houston Post, October 1983; id164249 (Ovsbox 25, Item 6)
    - "Arabian horse truly statuesque in sculptor Wilson’s rendering", Houston Chronicle, 1981; id164250 (Ovsbox 25, Item 7)
    - "Vice President George Bush…congratulates Richmond sculptor Bob G. Wilson on his Handsome Spirit of Freedom bronze horse that was presented to the Bushes as 1981 Houstonians of the Year", id164251 (Ovsbox 25, Item 8)
    - "Courtlandt Place Historical Association, Clean Houston join forces in holiday benefit", Houston Chronicle, December 1985; id164252 (Ovsbox 25, Item 9)
    - The Magazine of The Houston Post, December 1985; id164253 (Ovsbox 25, Item 10)
    - "Clean Houston looks proudly upon west programs", Houston Chronicle, February 1986; id164254 (Ovsbox 25, Item 11)
    - "KQUE’s Ronnie Renfrow adds new direction to busy career", Houston Chronicle, November 1985; id164255 (Ovsbox 25, Item 12)
    - "Christmas on Courtlandt Place", Houston Post, December 1985; id164256 (Ovsbox 25, Item 13)
    - Randall’s Flagship ad with Clean Houston promotion, April 1987; id164257 (Ovsbox 25, Item 14)
    - Randall’s Flagship ad with Clean Houston promotion, April 1987; id164258 (Ovsbox 25, Item 15)
    - "March of Dimes", Houston Post, January 1974; id164259 (Ovsbox 25, Item 16)
    - "Big City Beat" (March of Dimes mention), Houston Chronicle, October 1978; id164260 (Ovsbox 25, Item 17)
    - "University receives award: Flame of Truth Award honors Borman for contributions to higher education and mankind", Houston Chronicle, November 1978; id164261 (Ovsbox 25, Item 18)
    - "Patton’s son says phantom aided in battle", Houston Chronicle, November 1980; id164262 (Ovsbox 25, Item 19)
    - "UT stadium surprise leads to lengthy Hill Country ‘weekend'", Houston Post, November 1978; id164263 (Ovsbox 25, Item 20)
    - "West Point Cadets sing out", Houston Chronicle, January 1979; id164264 (Ovsbox 25, Item 21)
    - "Love for city shows in new book of photos", Houston Chronicle, October 1986; id164265 (Ovsbox 25, Item 22)
    - "The Houston Century", Houston Chronicle, December 1999; id164266 (Ovsbox 25, Item 23)
    - "Big City Beat" (WWL mention), Houston Chronicle, August 1982; id164267 (Ovsbox 25, Item 24)
    - "Prince Philip due in fall for wildlife fund-raiser", The Houston Post, July 1982; id164268 (Ovsbox 25, Item 25)
    - "11.6 million jobless as rate hits 10.4%", The Houston Post, November 1982; id164269 (Ovsbox 25, Item 26)
    - "Larger schools’ pay, facilities used in setting goals at TSU", Houston Post, November 1978; id164270 (Ovsbox 25, Item 27)
    - "Military might be a threat to democracy in Argentina", Houston Chronicle, November 1982; id164271 (Ovsbox 25, Item 28)
    - "Lindbergh a star in numerous areas", Houston Chronicle, May 1984; id164272 (Ovsbox 25, Item 29)
    - "Warm-up bash for benefit is royal hit", Houston Post, May 1984; id164273 (Ovsbox 25, Item 30)
    - "Doolittle honored here with Lindbergh Award", Houston Chronicle, May 1984; id164274 (Ovsbox 25, Item 31)
    - "Arts show a talent for raising funds", USA Today, 1980s; id164275 (Ovsbox 25, Item 32)
    - "Underwater eagle", Discover Magazine, August 1983; id164276 (Ovsbox 25, Item 33)
    - “Astronauts in Action on Tranquility Base, the Moon”, Houston Chronicle, August 1969; id164277 (Ovsbox 25, Item 34)
    - “Why Houston Should Have a Symphony Orchestra”, undated; id164278 (Ovsbox 25, Item 35)
    - “Arabian horse truly statuesque in sculptor Wilson’s rendering”, Houston Chronicle, September 1981; id164279 (Ovsbox 25, Item 36)
    - “Tribute to the Duke: Amateur artist fighting legal battle in effort to market statue of late actor John Wayne”, Houston Chronicle, March 1980; id164280 (Ovsbox 25, Item 37)
    - “Betty Jukes Heads Gala IX”, The United Methodist Reporter, The Spire, October 1984; id164281 (Ovsbox 25, Item 38)
    - Obituary for Ben Love, Houston Chronicle, January 2006; id164282 (Ovsbox 25, Item 39)
    - “Love Through the Years: Highlights in the life of Benton F. Love”, Houston Chronicle, January 2006; id164283 (Ovsbox 25, Item 40)
    - “M.D. Anderson role praised”, Houston Chronicle, January 2006; id164284 (Ovsbox 25, Item 41)
    - “Memorial service Saturday for ex-Chronicle publisher”, Houston Chronicle, January 2006; id164285 (Ovsbox 25, Item 42)
    - “City loses 2 business titans”, Houston Chronicle, January 2006; id164286 (Ovsbox 25, Item 43)
    - Commemorative page for Richard James Vaughn Johnson, Houston Chronicle, January 2006; id164287 (Ovsbox 25, Item 44)
    - “Where There’s a Harp, There’s a Milligan” (Houston Youth Symphony and Ballet mention), Houston Chronicle, March 1974; id164288 (Ovsbox 25, Item 45)
    - “In tune with youth: The Houston Youth Symphony and Ballet”, Houston Post, March 1974; id164289 (Ovsbox 25, Item 46)
    - “The Bob Herrings: Constant hosts have charity event formula: food, fun and fast”, Houston Chronicle, December 1979; id164290 (Ovsbox 25, Item 47)
    - “Comix Annex provides proving ground for developing jokesters”, Houston Post, August 1984; id164291 (Ovsbox 25, Item 48)
    - “Youth Symphony and Ballet to honor businessman as cultural leader”, Houston Chronicle, January 1983; id164292 (Ovsbox 25, Item 49)
    - “Top state court upholds decision against county: Epileptic awarded damages”, The Houston Post, January 1985; id164293 (Ovsbox 25, Item 50)
    - “Collective memories: For more than a century, mothers and daughters alike have been exploring educational, social, and philanthropic outlets as members of a handful of Houston women’s literary clubs”, Houston Chronicle, January 2000; id164294 (Ovsbox 25, Item 51)
    - “Green Tea today”, Houston Post, January 1974; id164295 (Ovsbox 25, Item 52)
    - “1997—1998 Fine Arts Calendar”, Houston Chronicle, August 1997; id164296 (Ovsbox 25, Item 53)
    - Houston Press fine arts calendar, February 1998; id164297 (Ovsbox 25, Item 54)
    - “A Gift of Music”, Houston Chronicle, September 1997; id164298 (Ovsbox 25, Item 55)
    - “Volunteer leadership honored”, Houston Chronicle, May 1997; id164299 (Ovsbox 25, Item 56)
    - “How Donors Can Keep Universities Honest”, The Wall Street Journal, September 1997; id164300 (Ovsbox 25, Item 57)
    - “Song sung at funeral”, Houston Chronicle, September 1997; id164301 (Ovsbox 25, Item 58)
    - “Sounds of music: Concert series to mark grand opening of UH music facility”, Houston Chronicle, September 1997; id164302 (Ovsbox 25, Item 59)
    - “HMM seeks $1 million in contributions”, Houston Chronicle, November 1983; id164303 (Ovsbox 25, Item 60)
    - “Fourth of July sparks continued success for “Dragnet””, Houston Post, July 1987; id164304 (Ovsbox 25, Item 61)
    - “Double the benefits: It was a night of nights at the Shamrock parties”, Houston Chronicle, October 1985; id164305 (Ovsbox 25, Item 62)
    - “Lights cast glow over first caroling ‘Movable Feast’”, Houston Chronicle, December 1985; id164306 (Ovsbox 25, Item 63)
    - “Potpourri” segment of The Houston Post, December 1985; id164307 (Ovsbox 25, Item 64)
    - “Oilers entering draft day with hope of moving up”, Houston Chronicle, April 1987; id164308 (Ovsbox 25, Item 65)
    - “Bottoming out: Houston hopes worst over”, Houston Post, March 1987; id164309 (Ovsbox 25, Item 66)
    - “Wildlife benefit honoree Prince Philip charms guests with casual air”, Houston Chronicle, November 1982; id164310 (Ovsbox 25, Item 67)
    - “Society Today: And the Legend Rolls On: Rolls Royce with a Legendary Past in St. Patrick’s Day Parade”, Houston Chronicle, March 1968; id164311 (Ovsbox 26, Item 1)
    - “Junior Woman’s Club President Welcomes New Members”, Houston Chronicle, February 1969; id164312 (Ovsbox 26, Item 2)
    - “Black Tie Dinner Climaxes Founder’s Week”, Orlando Evening Star, February 1967; id164313 (Ovsbox 26, Item 3)
    - “Junior Forum presents Showtime 74 May 3”, Westside News, May 1974; id164314 (Ovsbox 26, Item 4)
    - “Woman’s Club shares the wealth”, Houston Chronicle, April 1989; id164315 (Ovsbox 26, Item 5)
    - “75th Birthday is Observed”, The Houston Post, October 1968; id164316 (Ovsbox 26, Item 6)
    - Discovery Dateline newsletter, July 1999; id164317 (Ovsbox 26, Item 7)
    - “‘Civil War’ team heads to ‘Havana’”, Houston Chronicle, October 1998; id164318 (Ovsbox 26, Item 8)
    - “Former Egyptian first lady Sadat to speak here”, Houston Chronicle, August 1998; id164319 (Ovsbox 26, Item 9)
    - “Jehan Sadat honored for her work”, Houston Chronicle, October 1998; id164320 (Ovsbox 26, Item 10)
    - “Cast Trades Pajamas for Bathing Suits”, Houston Chronicle, June 1975; id164321 (Ovsbox 26, Item 11)
    - “New Directions opens program to help rehabilitate juveniles”, Houston Post, December 1974; id164322 (Ovsbox 26, Item 12)
    - “Two New Junior Clubs Help Mark a Diamond Anniversary”, Houston Chronicle, October 1968; id164323 (Ovsbox 26, Item 13)
    - “81st Birthday Luncheon of The Woman’s Club”, unknown source, November 1973; id164324 (Ovsbox 26, Item 14)
    - “Woman’s Club of Houston prepare for coming Club Year at their home”, Houston Post—Dispatch, November 1928; id164325 (Ovsbox 26, Item 15)
    - “Women’s Club to Host Autumn Art and Garden Tour”, Houston West Side Reporter, November 1972; id164326 (Ovsbox 26, Item 16)
    - “Society Today: Ice Is Nice”, Houston Chronicle, June 1972; id164327 (Ovsbox 26, Item 17)
    - “Gandhian activist tours U.S. to gain moral support from Indians here”, Houston Chronicle, April 1983; id164328 (Ovsbox 26, Item 18)
    - “America’s Pioneer Astronauts Strut the Right Stuff”, Star Magazine, March 1985; id164329 (Ovsbox 26, Item 19)
    - “Sally Ride worries that girls face bias against careers in science”, Minneapolis Star and Tribune, May 1985; id164330 (Ovsbox 26, Item 20)
    - “The Shuttle: America Poised for a Return to Space”, New York Times, April 1981; id164331 (Ovsbox 26, Item 21)
    - “Flight Plan Depicts Perils and Hopes”, New York Times, April 1981; id164332 (Ovsbox 26, Item 22)
    - “YMCA Plans National Program from People Who Have Had Heart Attacks”, Houston Chronicle, March 1976; id164333 (Ovsbox 26, Item 23)
    - “Although She Had Cancer, Author Refused Surgery”, Houston Chronicle, December 1972; id164334 (Ovsbox 26, Item 24)
    - “Beverly Sills Coming for Benefit”, Houston Chronicle, December 1972; id164335 (Ovsbox 26, Item 25)
    - “MOD chairwoman slated at dinner”, Westside News, December 1972; id164336 (Ovsbox 26, Item 26)
    - “March of Dimes Ball: Cocktail Party in the Clouds”, Houston Chronicle, March 1976; id164337 (Ovsbox 26, Item 27)
    - “Contemporary Arts Will Rock Back the Clock”, Houston Chronicle, July 1973; id164338 (Ovsbox 26, Item 28)
    - “MOD gala plans under way”, Houston Chronicle, February 1983; id164339 (Ovsbox 26, Item 29)
    - “The Mini Page”, Houston Chronicle, February 1983; id164340 (Ovsbox 26, Item 30)
    - Lindbergh Heritage Edition, 1985; id164341 (Ovsbox 26, Item 31)
    - “Art from the sea and soul”, Weekend News and Press, January 1985; id164342 (Ovsbox 26, Item 32)
    - “Houston Style Progress Review”, Houston Chronicle, January 1981; id164343 (Ovsbox 26, Item 33)
    - “Cadet Glee Club to Give Benefit Performance”, Suburbia-Reporter, February 1979; id164344 (Ovsbox 26, Item 34)
    - “West Point Cadet Glee Club to Appear”, Northwest News, March 1979; id164345 (Ovsbox 26, Item 35)
    - “Reveling in Houston’s art scene”, Houston Post, March 1981; id164346 (Ovsbox 26, Item 36)
    - “Spa to go feminine again, host 2 ex-Cabinet officials”, Houston Post, February 1981; id164347 (Ovsbox 26, Item 37)
    - “What do these women want? Peanut clusters to sports cars”, Houston Chronicle, February 1981; id164348 (Ovsbox 26, Item 38)
    - “600 fete club’s founder”, Houston Chronicle, November 1992; id164349 (Ovsbox 26, Item 39)
    - “Woman’s club celebrates 25th anniversary”, Houston Post, November 1992; id164350 (Ovsbox 26, Item 40)
    - “Ghoulish tours in LA and NY”, Houston Chronicle, October 1992; id164351 (Ovsbox 26, Item 41)
    - “Problems for Latin America: Birth Control Ban Will Have Little U.S. Effect, Expert Says”, Houston Chronicle, August 1968; id164352 (Ovsbox 26, Item 42)
    - “Teens Called Unprepared for Motherhood”, Houston Chronicle, August 1968; id164353 (Ovsbox 26, Item 43)